I believe that everyone will definitely not miss the Treasure Month’s choose-two-out-of-three horror treasure packs event.
After all, this is the biggest benefit in the past three seconds.
So which of these three horror bags is the most worth choosing and buying?
In this video, Xun won all the skins in advance at his own expense, bringing you a detailed hands-on evaluation of each skin.
The three scary treasure bags are Tesla Coil, Get Some French Fries and Hunting Time. First is the Tesla coil,
This fear treasure bag is undoubtedly the most frequently used. Not only does it have two permanent weapons of the Knowledge Circle,
S R3M is the strongest submachine gun in the current version.
In terms of appearance, there have been many modifications to the model. The overall texture is more metallic, with silver and black as the main colors.
There are copper wires and copper pipes throughout the gun body as embellishments. Customized accessories are mostly silver and red,
The overall design adopts an industrial technology style. Out of ten, I would give it an eight. The second one is to get some French fries.
The weapons are given to the current version of T zero-level firearms, Tamron and A W. After Shadow Wind,
Don't miss the second golden skin of A W. Birds and beasts. The appearance has been modified.
There are relatively few, and the attractive point is that the red and yellow colors are very bright.
Compared with the former, it has a very strong visual impact. The spray paint and letters on the gun body are the finishing touch.
Even if there are no modifications to the model, it is completely eye-catching and not monotonous at all. Customized accessories in gold and red,
It matches the color of the fries perfectly. As for this pistol, I feel like it’s just a make-believe. Just to mention it,
This pendant is quite nice. I would give it a seven out of ten.
So the last one is also my favorite hunting firearm, which is the G three Victor and M Yaoliu.
The exterior model has been modified very carefully, and the overall look is retro, with ivory white as the main color.
The most distinctive thing is the carvings and gold-drawn teeth that can be seen everywhere on the gun body. The custom accessories are also very well made.
The visor and gun stock have been very delicately modified. If you just look at the appearance, this one is far superior to the other two.
Due to the strength of M Yaoliu, it is destined that not many people will choose this skin. But if it is Ke Lao,
Jiangxun sincerely recommends collecting it. On a scale of ten, I would give it a nine-point five.